<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Old Books, New Attitudes</title><link>https://technologies-of-history.github.io/dyngley-edition/</link><description>Recent content on Old Books, New Attitudes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><copyright>Copyright © 2025</copyright><atom:link href="https://technologies-of-history.github.io/dyngley-edition/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introduction</title><link>https://technologies-of-history.github.io/dyngley-edition/introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://technologies-of-history.github.io/dyngley-edition/introduction/</guid><description>The Project Historians of medicine and science agree that something pivotal happened in England in the latter decades of the sixteenth century, as medieval theories about the body or the natural world diminished in the face of new discoveries, new ideas, and a new experimental method. And yet, the reading habits of sixteenth-century English artisans, bureaucrats, merchants, and farmers tell a different story, one that this project seeks to explore. Early modern English people were avid collectors of medieval manuscripts filled with centuries-old texts related to medicine, astrology, agriculture, or craft manufacture.</description></item><item><title>Folios</title><link>https://technologies-of-history.github.io/dyngley-edition/folios/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://technologies-of-history.github.io/dyngley-edition/folios/</guid><description/></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://technologies-of-history.github.io/dyngley-edition/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://technologies-of-history.github.io/dyngley-edition/about/</guid><description>Developing the Edition and Site This site was developed on a Hugo template hosted on GitHub pages. The linked repository contains the basic content for the site: the Introduction, About, Credit, and Resources pages. The data and metadata generated from the manuscript transcriptions and annotations are held in a separate GitHub repository, technologies-of-history/dyngley-data. The two repositories are linked to one another with EditionCrafter, a publication tool for digital critical editions under development by the Making and Knowing Project (M&amp;amp;K), Performant Software Solutions, and a number of case-study collaborators.</description></item><item><title>Credits</title><link>https://technologies-of-history.github.io/dyngley-edition/credits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://technologies-of-history.github.io/dyngley-edition/credits/</guid><description>Lead Editor Melissa Reynolds, Assistant Professor of History, Texas Christian University
Student Researchers Coming soon!</description></item></channel></rss>